{
    "id": "9255bb8002a14834bc2c8ea84b61abb2",
    "title": "Subordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The children were happy ………………….. the show began.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "as",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the place …………………. the accident occurred.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "when",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he worked hard, he couldn’t win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go ………………… he forbids me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "even if",
                "even as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She will not come ………………….. you invite her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she is pretty, I don’t like her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is surprising …………………. she didn’t invite you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here ………………… I come?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t go ………………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "because",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. the sky is overcast we will cancel the picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "That",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They say a silent prayer ………………. they start the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "before",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do ………………… you have been directed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "as",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}